Don Yoder collection of tape and disc recordings
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound Recordings
  - Sound recording, 1961 or before, RYQ 3066; 1 sound cassette (00:24:57): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR196)
    Recording of Emma Yoder.
    From the documentation: Don Yoder Collection #5.
  - Sound recording, January 13, 1951, RYQ 3067; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:15, Side B: 00:10:52): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR197)
    From the documentation: Don Yoder Collection #6.
    Rev. and Mrs. Martin were recorded on January 13, 1951. The other segments are undated. Side A ends abruptly.
    Start Rev. and Mrs. Wesley P. Martin (of the United Zion's Church), recorded in Akron, Pennsylvania, sing religious songs, in Pennsylvania German and English.
    00:25:00 An unidentified man sings religious songs in English, possibly bush meeting songs.
    00:35:57 Another unidentified man sings religious songs, in Pennsylvania German and English.
    00:40:23 A woman recites the Lord's Prayer.
    00:40:56 A man speaks about aspirin.
    00:41:41 An unidentified man sings "O Lord, Remember Me" and other religious songs in Pennsylvania German and English.
    From 00:05:07 to 00:05:27 only faint noise can be heard, as if a previous recording had been recorded over.
    Start An unidentified man sings religious songs, in Pennsylvania German and English.
    00:05:27 Two men sing religious songs in Pennsylvania German and English.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3068; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:15, Side: 00:18:45): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR198)
    From the documentation: Don Yoder Collection #7.
    Don Yoder speaks at a folk festival about dialect liturgy and the various forms of Pennsylvania German and Mose Dissinger stories. Others tell Dissinger stories, variously in Pennsylvania German and English, including Alfred Shoemaker, Ray Albright, Kenneth Mauer [?], Robert Hoppes (from Northampton County), Peter Kirshner (from Reading).
    The next program was the singing of Dutch choruses (listed in the program as "Pennsylvania Spiritual and Folksong Tradition." The singers were from the E.U.B. (Evangelical United Brethren) tradition. Singers include Lykens Valley Chorus, Harry Tobias, and Arthur Miller.
    This recording may be copied from another recording in the collection; see SR117.
    Content includes Dutch choruses, and Rev. Wesley Martin singing an old German hymn. See notes for Side A.
  - Sound recording, September 6, 1958, RYQ 3069; 1 sound cassette (00:33:04): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR199)
    According to the documentation, this is Frank Eckert II, recorded by Don Yoder.
    Eckart tells stories from Adams County, Pennsylvania, centered on witches.
    Sound cuts in and out until 00:00:28, when the recording continues without interruption.
  - Sound recording, May 15, 1961, RYQ 3070; 1 sound cassette (00:16:32): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR200)
    According to the documentation: "Evil eye remarks and interview - Mrs. Rose B. Green." Green makes remarks in English, and interviews a woman who speaks in Italian. Green provides the translation.
  - Sound recording, June 1970, RYQ 3071; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR201)
    René Grove, interviewed by Karen Thorsen
    This recording has not yet been digitized, so the content as described in the documentation awaits confirmation.
  - Sound recording, October 6 and 21, 1973, RYQ 3072; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:44, Side B: 00:46:39): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR202)
    Tape 1 of 5.
    Interview with Aaron Pepper (October 6, 1973). Continued on Side B.
    Conclusion of the interview with Aaron Pepper.
    From 00:12:51: interview with Anna Rabinowitz (October 21, 1973). Anna's husband, daughter, and Maltza Dobris are present for her interview. The interview cuts off at the end. Continued on Side B.
  - Sound recording, October 21, 1973; November 17-18, 1973, RYQ 3073; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:34, Side B: 00:46:28): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR203)
    Tape 2 of 5.
    Conclusion of the interview with Anna Rabinowitz (October 21, 1973). From 00:12:18: interview with Rubin Un (November 17-18, 1973). Present for Un's interview: Un, his wife, and the interviewer.
    Continuation of the interview with Rubin Un (November 17-18, 1973). The recording cuts off before the end of the interview.
  - Sound recording, November 18, 1973; December 1, 1973, RYQ 3074; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:39, Side B: 00:46:35): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR204)
    Tape 3 of 5. See notes for SR203.
    Continuation of the interview with Rubin Un (November 18 and December 1, 1973).
    Conclusion of the interview with Rubin Un (November 18 and December 1, 1973).
    From 00:30:37: interview with Aaron Pepper (December 1, 1973). Continued on SR205.
  - Sound recording, December 1-3, 1973, RYQ 3075; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:30:58, Side B: 00:31:00): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR205)
    Tape 4 of 5.
    Engineer's notes: There is tape machine noise throughout both sides. Channel imbalance throughout Side A, fluctuating imbalance throughout Side B. Flutter at tail end of both sides.
    Continuation of the interview with Aaron Pepper (December 1-2, 1973).
    Interview with Miriam "Maltza" Dobris, born July 16, 1897 (interviewed December 3, 1973). See SR206 for the conclusion of the Dobris interview.
  - Sound recording, December 3, 1973, RYQ 3076; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:20:38, Side B: 00:14:57): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR206)
    Tape 5 of 5. Conclusion of the interview with Miriam "Maltza" Dobris.
  - Sound recording, April 1981, RYQ 3077; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:17:27, Side B: 00:15:09): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo. (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR207)
    Susan Anderson interviews John Ruth (a Mennonite historian) about the history and meaning of plain clothing in the Mennonite tradition. Another man ("Joe") can also be heard on part of the recording.
    Anderson says she is writing on plain dress in the last 30-40 years.
    Engineer's notes: tape machine noise throughout both sides. Channel imbalance throughout Side A, fluctuating imbalance throughout Side B. Flutter at tail end of both sides.
  - Sound recording, May 1981, RYQ 3078; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:14:17, Side B: 00:30:13): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR208)
    Susan Anderson interviews John E. Lapp (a bishop). Another man's voice can be heard on the recording.
    According to the documentation: "John E. Lapp: A Bishop Talks About Plain Clothing" ("plain clothing in the Franconia conference," the oldest Mennonite body in the United States). This interview was part of Anderson's research for a paper; see note for SR207.
  - Sound recording, circa 1981, RYQ 3079; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:31:31, Side B: 00:29:56): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR209)
    Susan Anderson interviews Clarence Kulp on the topic of plain dress. A man named Joe can also be heard on the recording.
  - Sound recording, May 11, 1983, RYQ 3080; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:24:34, Side B: 00:09:42): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR210)
    Interview with Ruth Dreamdigger (R. Raham, interviewer?).
    Side A ends abruptly.
  - Sound recording, July 2, 1985, RYQ 3189; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:30:36, Side B: 00:30:44): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR211)
    Jenny [Jennie] Kopp Kehr (born 1892), interviewed by H. Griebel. Topics include Kehr's grandfather Leonard Kopp (a potter), and Pennsylvania German song and rhyme.
    Another woman is present, and participates in the interview. Side A ends abruptly. Sides A and B were misidentified before digitization, so the file identified as Side B is actually Side A, and vice versa.
  - Sound recording, July 24, 1985, RYQ 3190; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:20:48, Side B: 00:15:17): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR212)
    J. Norman Utz (age 82; born 1903, Newmarket, Frederick County, Maryland), interviewed by H. Griebel.
    Interview on his creativity: making violins, painting, writing hymns and poems; his childhood in Frederick County, Maryland.
    Discusses his music, especially religious music; plays accordion and two violins he built.
  - Sound recording, April 19, 1987, RYQ 3191; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:21, Side B: 00:46:27): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR213)
    Anna (Kerecz) Trescak, Theresa (Kerecz) Algeo, interviewed by Matthew W. Algeo on the subject of "Windisch Catholic Folk Practices in Bethlehem, Pennsylvania." Music unrelated to the interview and collection from 00:35:57 to the end of the recording.
    Noted on the documentation (possibly from Algeo): "the quality of this duplication leaves much to be desired."
    Engineer's notes: Right channel inactive on Side A, temporarily inactive on Side B. Content volume dips and becomes hard to hear throughout Side A and most of Side B.
  - Sound recording, February 25, 1992, RYQ 3192; 1 sound cassette (00:27:59): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR214)
    Art Christman's interview of his mother, Sylvia Christman. Subjects include people who were healers, people who believed in healing, the evil eye, and Jewish beliefs.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3193; 1 sound cassette (00:29:24): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR215)
    Henry Schwartz family (Geneva, Indiana): English, German, Swiss songs.
    Content on SR215 and SR216 is effectively the same.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3194; 1 sound cassette (00:29:00): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR216)
    See note for SR215.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3195; 1 sound cassette (00:19:32): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR217)
    Ora Watson: quilting, tape 2. Tape 1 is SR289.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3196; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:29:32, Side B: 00:29:22): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR218)
    From 00:03:00: Interview with Mrs. L.A. Swanson, of Clearfield, Pennsylvania, on folk medicine. From 00:09:23: the retired Rev. Keeler, of St. John's Lutheran Church, Bellefonte, Pennsylvania, on faith healing. Continued on Side B.
    Continuation of the interview with Rev. Keeler.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3197; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:41:46, Side B: 00:25:57): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR219)
    Interview with Mrs. Walter and Mrs. Elizabeth Janke (pronounced "yon-keez"), of Winburne, Pennsylvania, on folk medicine.
  - Sound recording, December 1, 1979, RYQ 3198; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:44:21, Side B: 00:44:27): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR220)
    "Quaker Culture in the Delaware Valley" - a one-day program at Winterthur Museum, Greenville, Delaware. Moderator: Dr. Don Yoder
    Side B ends abruptly.
  - Sound recording, May 10, 1980, RYQ 3199; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:30:39, Side B: 00:12:38): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 1 channel, Type I, mono (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR221)
    South Jersey Quaker History Harvest, Mullica Hill, New Jersey. Don Yoder's lecture is followed by a question-and-answer period.
    Both sides end abruptly.
  - Sound recording, April 13, 1981, RYQ 3200; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:43:04, Side B: 00:43:05): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR222)
    Don Yoder's lecture, "Oh, For a Thousand Tongues to Sing: Hymnody in Protestant Faith and Life." This lecture was third in the Spring 1981 Monday evening series at Pendle Hill, Wallingford, Pennsylvania. The series is entitled "Music and Worship: A Variety of Spiritual Experiences.
    Side B ends abruptly, during the start of the question-and-answer phase following the lecture. SR223 is a lower-quality copy of this tape.
  - Sound recording, April 13, 1981, RYQ 3201; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:42:45, Side B: 00:42:43): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR223)
    See SR222 for the better copy (according to the documentation). SR223 is the "poorer copy - drags" (according to the documentation).
  - Sound recording, March 8, 1986, RYQ 3202; 1 sound cassette (00:44:38): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR224)
    Don Yoder's lecture to the Pennsylvania Folklore Society, Bucknell, Pennsylvania.
    The recording begins abruptly.
  - Sound recording, March 26, 1988, RYQ 3203; 1 sound cassette (00:12:35): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR225)
    The recording begins with noise level tests, and about 00:03:00, an unidentified man gives a talk on grave markers in general and ethnic traditions regarding them. The talk is accompanied by sentimental music.
    According to the documentation, this should be Don Yoder's lecture on "Pennsylvania German Genealogy" (Seminar I) at LAWGS.
    The recording begins with noise level tests.
  - Sound recording, March 26, 1988, RYQ 3204; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:31:18, Side B: 00:15:51): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR226)
    Don Yoder's lecture on "Pennsylvania German Genealogy." LAWGS Seminar II.
  - Sound recording, March 26, 1988, RYQ 3205; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:45:19, Side B: 00:17:02): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR227)
    Don Yoder's lecture on "Swiss-German Emigration." LAWGS Seminar III.
  - Sound recording, April 22, 1995, RYQ 3206; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 01:03:40, Side B: 01:03:39): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR228)
    Don Yoder's lecture on "Methodism and the Pennsylvania Germans."
    Audio quality is very low and the speed is variable. The recording of Yoder on Side B ends at 00:03:27. The balance of the recording on that side is unrelated to the collection.
  - Sound recording, May 5, 2001, RYQ 3207; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:23, Side B: 00:46:23): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR229)
    Don Yoder's lecture on "Quakers in Early Centre County," at the FHA (Friends Historical Association) Spring meeting.
    On Side B the lecture is followed by a question-and-answer period.
  - Sound recording, 2003 or before, RYQ 3208; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:45:38, Side B: 00:14:09): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR230)
    Don Yoder's lecture on "The Reformed Church and Pennsylvania German Culture," at a Pennsylvania college or university. The respondent (on Side B) is Rev. Richard Druckenbrod.
    Druckenbrod died in 2003.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3209; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:59, Side B: 00:16:41): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR231)
    An unidentified lecture, given by Don Yoder. Topics include Mennonite meeting houses, Amish clothing, etc. Part of the presentation included a display of images. The lecture is followed by a question-and-answer period. From the documentation: "Don Yoder, #2"
    Audio recording levels are very low.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3210; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:25, Side B: 00:46:14): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR232)
    From the start to 00:07:43, two men speak about an election, a union, affiliation, etc. From 00:07:47, Don Yoder speaks about Centre Valley Quakerism to an unidentified audience. Continued on Side B.
    Conclusion of the lecture begun on Side A, ending at 00:37:50. Side B ends with unrelated print-through at a very low volume.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3211; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:45:56, Side B: 00:29:16): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR233)
    Don Yoder's lecture at Universitat Mainz, in Mainz, Germany.
  - Sound recording, undated, RYQ 3212; 1 sound cassette (00:48:29): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR234)
    Don Yoder's lecture on Quaker and Pennsylvania German genealogical research and finding ancestor's in Pennsylvania's Delaware Valley, to an audience in New Jersey.
  - Sound recording, January 31, 1974, RYQ 3213; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:52, Side B: 00:47:16): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR235)
    John Witthoft's lecture on "American Indian Folk Medicine," tape 1.
  - Sound recording, January 31, 1974, RYQ 3214; 1 sound cassette (00:18:43): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR236)
    John Witthoft's lecture on "American Indian Folk Medicine," tape 2.
  - Sound recording, March 21, 1975, RYQ 3215; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:45:37, Side B: 00:43:52): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR237)
    Lecture by Baba Ram Dass, at the University of Pennsylvania Museum auditorium, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
    Side A: relevant content begins at 00:02:04. Recording levels begin exceptionally low, and increase only slightly over the course of both tape sides.
  - Sound recording, June 17, 1980, RYQ 3216; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:13, Side B: 00:43:43): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR238)
    This tape appears to be a compilation from various sources.
    From the documentation: "L'Equipe de bon Vieux Temps" (Yvonne L. Lagasse). Lowell, Massachusetts. Copy of a sound reel.
    A woman sings a cappella in French. This ends at 00:16:12. At 00:16:13, a group sings in French, with piano accompaniment, followed by a man who sings in French, also with piano accompaniment, etc.
    Continued from Side A: songs in French, with piano accompaniment. At 00:30:45 a man interviews a woman; this part of the recording begins with the interview already in progress. The woman speaks in English and sings in French. The recording cuts off abruptly.
  - Sound recording, October 17, 1981, RYQ 3217; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:58, Side B: 00:33:59): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR239)
    Recorded at the Pennsylvania Historical Association's 50th annual meeting. The recording includes Donald B. Kelley's lecture on "Quaker Ecology"
  - Sound recording, April 22, 1982, RYQ 3218; 1 sound cassette (00:46:02): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR240)
    Two presentations in Don Yoder's Folklore 622 class: one by Peter Lowry and one by Glenn Hinson. Includes recorded samples of songs, as part of the presentations.
  - Sound recording, October 19, 1982, RYQ 3219; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:49, Side B: 00:28:52): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR241)
    Scott Swank's lecture on "Pennsylvania German Architecture and Furniture," for the Chester County Historical Society. From 00:19:00 to the end on Side B, there is content unrelated to the collection.
  - Sound recording, March 18, 1991, RYQ 3220; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:34:10, Side B: 00:14:13): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR242)
    Richard Druckenbrod: "Kurzweil unn [sic] Zeitverdreib." This appears to be a sermon, in Pennsylvania German.
    Archivist's note: "Kurzweil und Zeitverdreib" means "entertainment and pastime."
  - Sound recording, August 17, 2005, RYQ 3221; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:24:55, Side B: 00:28:09): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR243)
    From the documentation, this should be "Conversations with Dot Fry." However, both tape sides contain instrumental and vocal music, without an apparent relationship to the collection.
  - Sound recording, August 17, 2005, RYQ 3222; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:30:15, Side B: 00:30:14): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR244)
    Dialogues with Dot Fry, in Pennsylvania German.
    Archivist's note: Dot Fry was a Pennsylvania German storyteller and teacher. This interview may have been conducted by C. Richard Beam, who interviewed her at length and co-edited the interviews, which were published in 2014.
  - Sound recording, October 24 and 31, RYQ 3223; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:55:03, Side B: 00:43:14): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR245)
    A recording of Don Yoder's Folklife 550 class.
  - Sound recording, circa 1986, RYQ 3224; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:45:59, Side B: 00:46:04): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR246)
    Don Yoder's lecture on Pennsylvania German history and genealogy research, given in North Carolina as part of the FCGS German Workshop 2. This is tape 1; the lecture continues on SR247.
    Engineer's note: fluctuating channel imbalance and high frequency loss throughout both sides.
  - Sound recording, circa 1986, RYQ 3225; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:34, Side B: 00:46:57): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR247)
    FCGS German Workshop 2, tape 2. Continued from SR246; continued on SR248.
    Engineer's note: channel imbalance throughout both sides. Flutter and wow found on Side B.
  - Sound recording, circa 1986, RYQ 3226; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:46:01, Side B: 00:19:22): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR248)
    FCGS German Workshop 2, tape 3. Conclusion of Yoder's lecture and a question-and-answer period. The event continues from SR247; continued on SR249.
    Engineer's note: fluctuating channel imbalance throughout Side A, steady imbalance throughout Side B.
  - Sound recording, circa 1986, RYQ 3227; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:45:58, Side B: 00:39:11): analog, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR249)
    FCGS German Workshop 2, tape 4. Lecture by Rev. Richard Druckenbrod, titled "German Names on English Ears; or, What Do You Mean Joe Black is Really Johann Jakob Schwartz?" The event continues from SR248; continued on SR250.
    Engineer's notes: channel imbalance throughout Side A. Speed fluctuation opens Side A. Left channel of Side B is inactive for majority of recording. Static and high frequency loss throughout Side B.
  - Sound recording, circa 1986, RYQ 3228; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:20:06, Side B: 00:21:20): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR250)
    FCGS German Workshop 2, tape 5. Continued from SR249. Side B is the beginning of a talk by an unidentified male speaker.
    Engineer's note: channel imbalance throughout both sides.
  - Sound recording, February 1, 1964, RYQ 3229; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:47:09, Side B: 00:47:12): analog, 2 channels, Type II, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR251)
    Pennsylvania Dutch service, with Rev. Paul D. Yoder. Theme of the sermon: "I am the Way." (Pennsylvania Dutch Society of St. Jacob's Union Church; Jefferson, York County, Pennsylvania). The church was known as "the stone church."
    Engineer's note: channel imbalance throughout both sides. Sped fluctuation opens Side A.
  - Sound recording, December 31, 1972 and 1973, RYQ 3230; 1 sound cassette (Side A: 00:47:15, Side B: 00:32:42): analog, 1 7/8 ips, 2 channels, Type I, stereo (Item-id AFC 2003/051: SR252)
    Engineer's notes: static noise throughout both sides. Vocal distortion finishes out Side A. Channel imbalance throughout Side A, fluctuating imbalance throughout Side B. Low Level occurs on both sides.
    Side A (December 31, 1972)